reprint-content.com 2008-07-23

# Article Distribution Services : Reprint Articles Directory

Reprint-Content.com Privacy Policy

This privacy policy tells you how reprint-content.com uses personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed at our discretion, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

Collection of Information

From time to time we may collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill specific requests from visitors and/or to help us provide better service to our users. This information is only used to fulfill your specific requests, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and other tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. This allows us to improve our service for all users. Cookies can also help customize the reprint-content.com for visitors and members. Personal information about you or your computer cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. In some cases however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information (i.e. non-personally identifiable information) may be shared with third parties (for example total number of visitors to the site in one month).

Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Under no circumstances will we rent, sell, or otherwise give out any personally identifiable information to any third party. 

Commitment to Data Security 

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All email messages and newsletters from this site will contain a web link that allows you to immediately opt out of further mailings. 

Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: privacy@reprint-content.com  
regular mail:  
Kaizen Publishing Inc.  
17 Southview Cres.  
Ottawa, On.  
K2E 5R4  
By Phone: 613-225-7642  

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
